<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Live Streaming on Tencent Cloud on English</title>
    <link>/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Live Streaming on Tencent Cloud on English</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Live Streaming for UGC or M&amp;E</title>
      <link>/css/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/css/index.html</guid>
      <description>CSS is a all-in-one fully managed service to provide reliable, high-quality, low-latency live streaming easily and conveniently. CSS helps you configure your live streaming lifecycle quickly and easily by templates that allow you to quickly and easily create and delete live channels. After configuring your CSS channel using a template and getting your live feed into the cloud, you can get the playback URL. This means CSS manages the transcoding, packaging, and reliably delivers streaming video to viewers through the CSS CDN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live Streaming for large events or OTT</title>
      <link>/stream_css/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/stream_css/index.html</guid>
      <description>Tencent Cloud provides media services that can meet almost all customer use cases, from live streaming to video on demand.
As described in previous section, CSS is a fully managed all-in-one service to provide stable, high-quality, low-latency live streaming easily and conveniently.
CSS can be configured with Push and Player domain, and Player domain in here provides CDN capability for optimized live streaming. CSS Player domain is natively integrated with CSS Push domains, or integrated with other live streaming origination services by enabling Origin-Pull mode.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>